Royal Matchmaker is a romance, tv movie film directed by Mike Rohl.
A struggling NYC matchmaker is hired by a king to find his son a
suitable wife in time for a national celebration.
As the clock ticks towards her deadline, the matchmaker finds him the perfect
wife -- only to realize that she’s fallen in love with him!
Kate Gleason, played by Bethany Joy Lenz.
Prince Sebastian, played by Will Kemp.
Britney Van Howell, played by Brittany Bristow.
Countess Petra Petrovich, played by Elva Trill.
King Edward, played by Simon Dutton.
Loraine Paisley, played by Poppy Roe.
The Princess and the Matchmaker (Korean: 궁합) is a 2018 South Korean
period romantic comedy film directed by Hong Chang-pyo.
The film stars Shim Eun-kyung, Lee Seung-gi, Kim Sang-kyung, Yeon
Woo-jin, Kang Min-hyuk, Choi Woo-shik and Jo Bok-rae.
The film tells story of a saju expert, Seo Do-yoon, who received an order from the King to help
him pick a husband for his daughter, Princess Song-hwa, based on their fortune.
It is the second installment of Jupiter Film's three-part film project on the Korean fortune-telling traditions,
following The Face Reader which was released in 2013 and followed by Feng Shui later in 2018.
The film explores themes of prince, royalty, matchmaker, hallmark.
The tone is emotional.